okay hello everyone and thank you very
好的，大家好，非常感谢
much for coming to our session we
参加我们的会议很重要
appreciate there's a whole bunch of
欣赏有一大堆
really good sessions so so thank you for
会议真的很好，所以谢谢你
for joining our one my name is simon
因为加入我们，我叫西蒙
maple this is my colleague oleg slave
枫，这是我的同事奥格奴隶
hello everyone and this is a session on
大家好，这是一个会议
good-cop bad-cop guide to java 9 so
好警察坏警察指南到Java 9所以
who's heard of Java 9 so far in Java 1
迄今为止在Java 1中听说过Java 9的人
most people I would expect that on a
大多数人，我希望
Wednesday so we're gonna do a slightly
星期三，所以我们要稍微
subtly different outlook on on this
对此有不同的看法
session it's not just gonna be a regular
会议，这不仅会成为常规
session we're gonna be a good cop and a
会议，我们将成为一个好警察和
bad cop so that's first of all introduce
坏警察，所以首先来介绍
ourselves yeah this is me my name is
自己，是的，这是我，我的名字是
Alex wife I come from Estonia I work for
我从爱沙尼亚工作的亚历克斯妻子
a company called zero to round as a
被称为零到四舍五入的公司
developer advocate there are a couple of
开发者倡导者有几个
things that I do I maintain our blog
我要做的事情我维护我们的博客
called rebel apps where we publish
在我们发布的地方称为反叛应用
technical content so if you go check it
技术含量，如果您去检查
out
出
it will make me personally very happy
这会让我个人很开心
I'm a co-leader with Simon of a virtual
我和西蒙（Simon）共同领导
drug which is the Java online only Java
这是Java在线药品Java
user group so if you're lazy enough to
用户组，因此，如果您足够懒惰
join your local Java user group we will
加入您的本地Java用户组，我们将
welcome you and we'll be happy to have
欢迎您，我们将很高兴拥有
you and I'm also a leader of GDG group
您和我也是GDG集团的负责人
in party in Estonia which is a very
在爱沙尼亚的聚会上
small town but a very proud one so I
小镇，但非常自豪，所以我
also work with a London jug and the
还与伦敦水罐和
virtual jug and I work in developer
虚拟水罐，我在开发人员中工作
relations as well so I work as a
关系，所以我以
developer advocate for zero turnaround
开发者倡导零周转
but yeah let's get started so Java 9 the
但是，让我们开始吧，所以Java 9
debate the way this is going to work is
辩论这将如何工作的方式是
we're gonna play good-cop bad-cop
我们要扮演好警察坏警察
we're gonna take a number of the major
我们将采取一些主要
Java know and some of the minor Java 9
Java知识和一些次要Java 9
updates and one of us is going to play a
更新，我们中的一个将扮演
good cop one of us is gonna play a bad
好警察我们中的一个会扮演坏人
cop so the good cop will look at some of
警察，所以好的警察会看一些
the positive parts of that feature the
积极的方面具有
bad cop will look at perhaps some of the
坏警察会看一些
parts of that feature which aren't so
该功能的某些部分并非如此
good and when you as the jury have heard
好，陪审团当您听到
both the pros and the cons you will vote
您将投票的利弊
as to whether you like that feature in
关于您是否喜欢该功能
Java 9 or not or whether it's something
是否使用Java 9或是否是Java 9
enough for you to migrate up perhaps the
足以让您迁移
way it were
过去的样子
taxes if I'm good cop or I'm bad cop you
如果我是好警察或我是坏警察向你征税
always vote for whatever I say because I
总是投票支持我所说的一切，因为我
like to win and just ignore Oleg really
喜欢赢球，只是无视奥列格
that's probably what I'll what I'll say
那可能就是我要说的
so that starts before I start before we
这样在我开始之前就开始
start let's not get into this debate so
开始让我们不要参与这场辩论，所以
fast who is excited so John 9 was
斋戒谁兴奋，所以约翰9是
cooking for a long time and then it was
煮了很长时间，然后
released and people some people are
被释放，有人
excited about that some people are not
感到兴奋的是有些人没有
that excited about that
对此感到兴奋
so let's vote in the beginning of this
所以让我们在开始时投票
session before we hurt all our arguments
会议之前，我们伤害了我们所有的论点
whether it's good or bad who is excited
兴奋是好是坏
about John I see yeah if you do that in
关于约翰，我知道是的，如果你这样做
Estonia that would never happen that
爱沙尼亚那将永远不会发生
would never happen we might have a guest
永远不会发生，我们可能会有客人
from somewhere yeah welcome Paul who is
从某个地方欢迎保罗
not excited about John 9 and it's kind
对约翰9感到不高兴，这很友善
of disappointed with this release few
对此版本感到失望的
people ok right so let's start shall we
人们没事吧，让我们开始吧
yep modularity the elephant in the room
是的模块化房间里的大象
the Mafia the big elephant in the room
黑手党房间里的大象
so modularity why do we need modularity
那么模块化为什么我们需要模块化
well we have modularity in a couple of
好吧，我们有几个模块化
different ways we have platform
我们拥有平台的不同方式
modularity and we have application
模块化，我们有应用
modularity we really need platform
我们真正需要平台的模块化
modularity because the way the the
模块化，因为方式
platform has got over many many years
平台已经有很多年了
requiring backwards compatibility it's
需要向后兼容
turned into really the elephant in the
变成了真正的大象
room right it's a huge beast that we
房间对，这是一个巨大的野兽，我们
need to support horrible things like
需要支持可怕的事情，例如
clobber who likes core bar nope no
喜欢核心棒的炸弹
whooping no okay
百无聊赖
we don't like clobber but why do we have
我们不喜欢clo，但是为什么我们有
to have it because we have to support
拥有它，因为我们必须支持
really old apps that need core bar okay
真正需要核心功能的旧应用
but even if we don't want to use core
但即使我们不想使用核心
but we have to still have it as part of
但我们仍然必须将其作为
our platform so what we do is we
我们的平台，所以我们要做的是
modernize the platform into modules that
将平台现代化为模块
we can choose whether we want to have in
我们可以选择是否要加入
in in our runtime or not and depending
是否在我们的运行时中并取决于
on what our application needs from its
从我们的应用程序需要什么
from its platform we can bundle up a new
从它的平台，我们可以捆绑一个新的
runtime which only provides that so
运行时只提供了这样
we're creating a runtime based on the
我们正在基于
needs of our application rather than
我们应用程序的需求，而不是
having this one-size-fits-all JVM and it
有一个适合所有人的JVM，
is a big size fits all JVM for any
大尺寸适合所有JVM
application that wants to run on that
要在其上运行的应用程序
job platform you'll notice at the bottom
您会在底部看到的工作平台
here we have the the Java based class
这里我们有基于Java的类
this is this is the fundamental class
这是基础课
which every
每个
and everything must use it contains
所有必须使用的内容都包含
things like your collections everything
像您收藏的东西
that you need to use if you want any
如果需要，您需要使用
kind of java application we also have
我们也有一种Java应用程序
some compact profiles there which you
那里有一些紧凑的配置文件
may recognize from other things the
可能从其他事物中认识到
lines our dependency so if you if you
排队我们的依赖关系，所以如果你如果你
require a specific bundle
需要特定的捆绑包
that's like module I'm an OS GI person
就像模块，我是OS GI人
as well so this is Hertz if you require
同样，如果您需要，这是赫兹
a certain module like let's say here we
像我们在这里说的某个模块
have scripting that module will in turn
具有该模块将依次执行的脚本
depend on base so depending on which
取决于基础，因此取决于哪个
modules you require you'll build up this
您需要的模块将构建此模块
dependency tree okay we deal with
依赖树好吧，我们处理
modularity already when we design things
我们在设计事物时就已经有了模块化
we draw boxes we write words in the
我们画框，我们在
boxes and we draw arrows between them we
框，我们在它们之间绘制箭头
design in a modular way so when we write
设计以模块化的方式，所以当我们写
code we write it very very flat okay we
代码我们写得非常平坦好吧，我们
don't actually put push that into into a
实际上不要将其推入
modularity into a modular way and the
模块化成模块化的方式
reason is up till now we haven't had in
原因到现在为止，我们还没有参加
any enforcement in our runtime now
现在在我们的运行时中执行任何强制措施
whether we're compiling or whether we're
我们是在编译还是在
actually running in the runtime that the
实际上在运行时
platform will always enforced modularity
平台将始终执行模块化
we can't compile against something if if
如果，如果
a module structure that determines that
确定以下内容的模块结构：
we don't actually depend on that module
我们实际上并不依赖那个模块
likewise in our runtime we can't start
同样在我们的运行时，我们无法启动
our runtime unless all the modules are
我们的运行时，除非所有模块
present for that for the application to
目前为该应用程序
run so very very key both in compilation
在编译时都非常关键
and during runtime that the module
在运行期间
structure must be satisfied for us to
结构必须满足我们的要求
come to fully compile or fully run
完全编译或完全运行
that's very important but this is the
这很重要，但这是
first time we've had enforcement now yes
第一次我们现在有执法了
we have the module path we still have
我们有模块路径
the class path so if you wanted to still
上课的路径，所以如果你仍然想
use the class path you can although
尽管可以使用类路径
under the covers everything is still
在幕后一切依旧
modular in in the platform so you can't
在平台中模块化，因此您无法
use things that are hidden from you so
使用对你隐藏的东西
what's hidden from you well in modules
模块中对您隐藏的是什么
you have encapsulation what the module
你有封装什么模块
exports is what other modules can use
导出是其他模块可以使用的
what the module depends on what it
什么模块取决于它
requires
要求
that's that creates the module growth so
那就是导致模块增长的原因
if a client applications running on the
如果客户端应用程序在
class box it's still running on a
类框仍在运行
modular JVM but if you choose to use the
模块化JVM，但如果您选择使用
module path in your application then
然后在您的应用程序中使用模块路径
both your both your platform and your
您的平台和您的
application will be running in a modular
应用程序将在模块化中运行
way but you don't
方式，但你不
soli need to do both wow that looks
soli需要做两个看起来都不错的哇
painful doesn't it as a result the
结果不是很痛苦吗
unsafe API which many of you have heard
许多人都听说过的不安全的API
of mostly probably frameworks and
大多数可能是框架和
libraries the unsafe API is is going to
库不安全的API将要
be hidden from you it was an API which
对您隐藏这是一个API
was which was meant to be an internal
原本是内部的
API but as I said before there is no
API，但正如我之前所说，
enforcement previously so people were
以前是执法的，所以人们
using it and actually for good reason
使用它，实际上是有充分理由的
because there's some great stuff in
因为里面有很棒的东西
there and it's made our ecosystem richer
在那里，这使我们的生态系统更加丰富
let's let's do a demo Jack should we see
让我们做一个演示杰克，我们应该看看
we see a demo actually you've probably
我们实际上看到了一个演示
already seen how module invoke Java is
已经知道模块如何调用Java
anyone's in knots in a module demo got a
在模块演示中任何陷入困境的人都有
few people I'll show you I'll show you a
几个人给我看，我给你看
demo just with services so I'm gonna go
演示服务，所以我要去
over to IntelliJ let's clear some of
转到IntelliJ，让我们清除一些
this up so in IntelliJ right now I have
所以在IntelliJ中，我现在有
I have three modules 3 j9 modules I have
我有三个模块我有三个j9模块
0 turn under API and let's start with
在API下旋转0，让我们开始
consumer consumer is our consumer module
消费者消费者是我们的消费者模块
that actually goes to the provider via
实际上通过
an API now our API if we just quickly
一个API现在就是我们的API
have a look at that is right API is very
看一下对吧，API非常
simple it's got my service and it just
很简单，这就是我的服务，
has a single method called get message
有一个称为get message的方法
in our module info Java we just export
在我们的模块信息Java中，我们只是导出
that package so this is a module
那个包，所以这是一个模块
containing code that is then exposed to
包含然后暴露给
the rest of the module system consumer
其余模块系统使用者
where's our consumer here no that's our
我们的消费者在哪里，不，那是我们的
provider sorry a consumer here has a
提供者抱歉，这里的消费者有一个
single class called consumer wow that's
单班叫消费者哇，这是
not Mary yeah that's not very good is
不是玛丽，是的，不是很好
that ok a consumer just has a main
好的，消费者只有一个主要
method it spins around in a loop calling
它在循环调用中旋转的方法
cool services cool services just does a
很棒的服务很棒的服务
system print out of a counter looking
系统打印出柜台外观
for services that count is incremented
对于计数递增的服务
we sleep for a second and then we print
我们睡一秒钟，然后打印
out nothing at all so it does pretty
一点都没有出来，所以它很漂亮
much nothing yeah but there's a little
是的，没什么，但是有一点
spoiler for you in the middle which we
在我们中间为您扰流
won't talk about just yet the next thing
不会再谈论下一件事
is the provider and the provider in pull
是提供者，而拉中的提供者
all the provider in pull does is the
拉的提供者所要做的就是
provider in pull implements my service
提供者实施我的服务
and implements they get message method
并实现他们获取消息方法
okay so we have a provider which
好的，所以我们有一个提供商
implements the service we have a
实施我们拥有的服务
consumer which will soon grab that
消费者将很快抓住
service and that's pretty much it so I'm
服务，仅此而已，所以我
going to run this I might even run it
要运行它，我什至可以运行它
using durable so we will get a code and
使用持久性，所以我们将获得一个代码，
update it as we as we go as jeribai
像jeribai一样更新它
loading and now here we have our loop
加载，现在我们在这里循环
looking for services but there's no
寻找服务，但没有
services there so how do we actually use
服务在那里，我们如何实际使用
services well we use it by the service
服务很好，我们用它来服务
loader and the service layer is actually
加载程序和服务层实际上是
something which was what 1/6 maybe 1/4
是1/6也许是1/4的东西
something like that and it's been there
像那样的东西，它在那里
and and the modularity system uses the
并且模块化系统使用
same service loader we can register
我们可以注册的服务加载程序
things with it and we can grab grab
事情，我们可以抓住
services from there so what I'm going to
那里的服务，所以我要去
do is first of all I'm going to actually
首先要做的是
make sure we're using the service loader
确保我们正在使用服务加载器
so in a consumer and a module what I'm
所以在消费者和模块中，我是
going to say here is I'm gonna say that
要说的是我要说的是
we use a specific service so that's
我们使用特定服务，因此
going to be a hero turn around or API
将成为英雄转身或API
dot my service so we're now saying that
点我的服务，所以我们现在要说
we're going to be using that service so
我们将使用该服务，因此
I'm gonna hit save I'm gonna rebuild my
我要点击保存，我要重建我的
application there we go so that's been
我们去那里的应用程序
reloaded live into the environment still
重新将生活重新加载到环境中
not got any services and the one of the
没有任何服务，其中之一
reasons for that is well we're not
原因很好，我们不是
actually grabbing any services from the
实际上是从
service loader so I'm going to come back
服务加载器，所以我要回来
in here I'm gonna uncomment this this is
在这里我要取消注释这是
a great way this is a great new style of
这是一种很棒的新风格
development it's called development via
开发称为开发
uncoding you get far fewer bugs it's
取消编码，您得到的错误少得多
amazing I don't know why more people
太神奇了，我不知道为什么会有更多的人
don't do it so we go to the service
不要这样做，所以我们去了服务
loader we say load all services or the
加载程序，我们说加载所有服务或
interface my service we actually get
接口我实际上得到的服务
iterable back of my services we go
我们的服务很糟糕
through that and we just try and call
通过那个，我们只是尝试打电话
get message on that so I'm going to hit
得到消息，所以我要打
save I'm gonna reload that into my
保存，我要重新加载到我的
runtime and there we go it's reloaded
运行时，我们去了它重新加载
but we're still not getting anything
但是我们还是什么也没得到
back and that's because no services have
返回，那是因为没有服务
been registered now the way to register
现在已经注册了注册方式
a service is in my provider class here
服务在我的提供程序类中
we go provider
我们去提供者
imple we have our provider input which I
简单来说，我们有我们的提供者输入
showed you in our module info dot Java
在模块信息中向您展示了Java
what we actually need to say is we need
我们实际上需要说的是
to say what we're going to do is were
说我们要做的是
going to provide
要提供
the the class org dot zero turn just get
该类组织点零转刚得到
rid of that turn around
摆脱那转身
dot API dot my service and we're going
点API点我的服务，我们要去
to provide that oops we're going to
为了提供这些信息，我们将
provide that with the org dot zero turn
提供零点转向的组织机构
around dots
点周围
provider dot provider
提供者点提供者
imple so we're saying we're going to
简单，所以我们说我们要
provide the service and here is our
提供服务，这是我们的
implementation and what that's going to
实施以及将要做什么
do when I save that and f9 that that's
当我保存它并做f9那就是
going to reload in and all of a sudden
要重新加载，突然之间
we're getting a service back our service
我们正在获得服务回馈
is just returning underscore what that
只是返回下划线是什么
simple provides messages does is that
简单提供的消息确实是
the the Java Runtime is under the covers
Java Runtime是隐藏的
registering that service with the
向该服务注册该服务
service loader and then when we actually
服务加载器，然后当我们实际
use that by another by another module
由另一个模块由另一个使用
and actually perform a lookup into our
并实际上对我们进行查找
our service load we're grabbing that
我们的服务负担
service back and just to prove that that
服务回来，只是为了证明
is the service I can go into our
是我可以提供给我们的服务
provider amplify wanted to and let's say
提供者放大了想要说的
let's say this is from Plus this get
假设这是从Plus得到的
class oops
班级糟糕
darts and get name hit save let's relate
飞镖并击中名称，让我们联系一下
that and then you'll get the name of the
然后，您将获得名称
class which is oops there we go
哎呀，我们上课了
from water turnaround or provider in
来自水的周转或供应商
pool so that's that's the modules will
池，这就是模块将
go
走
so that's Java nine modules before we go
所以这是Java的九个模块
on to much more just want to say the
只是想说更多
modules hasn't just been available there
模块不仅在那里可用
for the platform and to allow us to have
平台，并让我们拥有
more modular applications but because of
更多的模块化应用程序，但是由于
the module system I'm sure all of you
模块系统，我敢肯定
have heard of the new release cadence in
听说过新的发行节奏
Java going forward it's gonna be every
Java向前发展将是每一个
six months so next March we're gonna
六个月，所以明年三月
have what it's likely gonna be called an
有可能被称为
18.3 release their next September we're
18.3发布他们的下一个九月
gonna have an 18.9 release the reason
要发布18.9的原因
this is possible is cuz of the module
这是模块的cuz
system by having me by having everything
通过拥有一切让我拥有
as modules it's much much easier to make
作为模块，制作起来要容易得多
our updates and push that into that push
我们的更新并将其推送到
that into the new runtime with it you
与它一起进入新的运行时
know in a single module without having
在一个模块中知道而无需
too many dependencies on other modules
对其他模块的依赖过多
we can also
我们也可以
a tool called j-link which allows us to
一个名为j-link的工具，它使我们能够
reduce the size of our runtime using
减少使用的运行时大小
j-link we can say this is my application
j-link我们可以说这是我的应用
provide me with a Java image that will
为我提供一个Java映像，它将
allow you to only use the platform
只允许您使用平台
modules you need and it will provide you
您需要的模块，它将为您提供
with like a 40 mega image rather than
像一张40兆的图片，而不是
this huge image and that will that will
这个巨大的形象，那将会
allow you to run that you know the JVM
允许您运行知道JVM的信息
with your application and it's much much
与您的应用程序有关
faster smaller footprint and also
更快的更小的占位空间
incubators we'll talk a little bit about
孵化器，我们将谈论一些
HTTP 2 later but it wasn't ready because
HTTP 2之后，但尚未准备就绪，因为
we needed more community feedback but
我们需要更多的社区反馈，但
now what we can do is we can release a
现在我们可以做的是释放一个
module as an incubator which will allow
模块作为孵化器，将允许
for that community feedback and then a
对于该社区的反馈，然后
later stage we push it into the main
后期我们将其推入主要
open JDK so not only as modules provide
打开JDK，所以不仅要提供模块
us with a much nicer way of of
我们以更好的方式
developing our code but it is also
开发我们的代码，但这也是
allowed us with all these new freedoms
赋予我们所有这些新自由
to release Java quicker to have smaller
更快地发布Java以使其更小
runtimes and to actually you know play
运行时，实际上你知道玩
with Java and more with incubators so I
Java和更多孵化器，所以我
think we should just vote now I don't
认为我们应该现在就投票我不
think there's a bad cop in here is there
认为这里有一个坏警察
that's good
那很好
that's pretty amazing modules are
相当惊人的模块是
excellent as the salmon said we have a
鲑鱼说的很棒，我们有一个
smaller footprint we have faster release
占用空间更小，发布速度更快
cadence which has nothing to do with
节奏与无关
modules but the features who can get
模块，但谁可以得到的功能
there sooner so before we go forward we
早一点，所以在我们前进之前
we need to assess every feature not just
我们需要评估每个功能，而不仅仅是
by what it gives us or what other people
通过它给我们或其他人带来什么
say it gives us but what it actually
说它给了我们，但实际上是什么
does it solve a problem for us and we
它为我们解决了一个问题吗？
have to remember that modules built in
必须记住内置的模块
the JDK as they are were designed to
JDK旨在
solve a problem for the JDK developers
为JDK开发人员解决问题
it wasn't in the jab it wasn't any plan
这不是在戳刺中，没有任何计划
to devise a modular system to build
设计一个模块化系统来构建
consumer applications from scratch we
从零开始的消费者应用程序
had that opportunity to have OSGi in our
有机会在我们的OSGi
systems right we didn't choose that most
对的系统，我们没有选择那么多
of us didn't choose that create so enjoy
我们当中的人没有选择创造，而是享受
excellent
优秀的
you're good people some of us didn't
你是好人，我们中有些人没有
choose that and and so module sauce
选择那个，等等模块酱
really nice problem of development open
真正好的开发问题
JDK and enforcing the rules and
JDK并执行规则和
integrity of the open JDK better
完整的开放式JDK更好
but what is the cost because it's very
但是成本是多少，因为它非常
simple on the language level that this
在语言层面上，这很简单
is like five new keywords a new module
就像五个新关键字组成一个新模块
info file and a lot of pain was actually
信息文件，实际上很多痛苦
migrating old projects to the Java nine
将旧项目迁移到Java 9
if you work on the greenfield projects
如果您从事未开发的项目
you've starts from scratch this is
你从头开始，这是
amazing and you would love it if you
很棒，如果您愿意，您会喜欢的
actually have an application that is
实际上有一个应用程序是
several gigabytes several thousand files
几千兆字节几千个文件
big then you would perhaps have a
大那么你可能会有一个
problem you would have a problem with
问题，你会遇到一个问题
the build systems we will have a problem
构建系统，我们将有一个问题
with ecosystem where some some libraries
拥有一些图书馆的生态系统
don't actually migrate whom were
实际上不迁移谁
unsupported or maintained any further
没有任何支持或维护
and all that can cause you trouble so
一切都会给你带来麻烦
when you are getting excited about the
当您对
modules you have to know that there is a
您必须知道有一个模块
migration path so before the migration
迁移路径，因此在迁移之前
path was a little bit unclear up to the
路径有点不清楚
very last moment of the release of Java
Java发行的最后一刻
9 but currently we think that this is
9但目前我们认为这是
the idea of how to migrate further so
如何进一步迁移的想法
what do you want to do you don't want to
你想做什么你不想
upgrade to the development environment
升级到开发环境
immediately it starts module rising
立即启动模块上升
everything what you want to do you want
你想做的一切
to upgrade if you cannot upgrade your
如果无法升级，则升级
production environment out of the blue
生产环境突飞猛进
because that's just unwise so you want
因为那是不明智的，所以你想要
to upgrade your staging environment or
升级您的暂存环境或
something where you can try it out you
可以尝试的东西
can benefit from the other improvements
可以从其他改进中受益
that are in John 9 and then you want to
在约翰福音第9章中，然后您想
fix the easiest things that you can
解决最简单的事情
potentially fix concerning the module
可能修复有关模块的问题
system currently it is not enforced to
系统当前未强制执行
the very strictest level by default but
默认情况下最严格的级别，但是
you can turn it on if you want if you
您可以根据需要打开它
want additional work fixing those Earths
需要更多的工作来修复那些地球
but you can fix the warnings and then
但您可以修正警告，然后
you wait for some time preferably
你最好等一段时间
somewhere until April 2018 first you
直到2018年4月为止的某个地方
will have the new major release of Java
将具有Java的新主要版本
and second probably the ACA's system
其次可能是ACA的系统
will catch up and you can migrate to
将赶上，您可以迁移到
modules bottoms up starting from the
模块从
libraries you can also migrate the other
您还可以迁移其他库
way around but it's much harder so when
到处走，但要困难得多，所以当
you think about the modules keep this
您考虑模块保留此
picture in mind out of those two people
那两个人心中的画面
who they think is a developer and who is
他们认为谁是开发商，谁是谁
an architect
一位建筑师
the feature the like modules will
类似模块的功能
benefit architecture concerns vary
利益架构关注点各不相同
greatly but for a developer it could be
很大，但对于开发人员来说，可能是
a lot of pain so the good thing is
很多痛苦，所以好事是
unsafe is still accessible so we can do
不安全仍然可以访问，所以我们可以做
stuff under the covers
隐藏的东西
so modularity
如此模块化
let's boot so who thinks who thinks that
让我们启动，以便谁思考谁在想
modularity has saved the Java language
模块化节省了Java语言
and is has actually made the Java
并且实际上已经使Java
language more sustainable for the future
语言对未来更具可持续性
who believes that modularity is a good
谁认为模块化是一个好选择
thing in Java 9 there we go there we go
Java 9中的东西
ok who believes that Java and release
好吧，谁相信Java和发布
and migration will not be easy I believe
我相信迁移并不容易
uh but that's not that's not the
嗯，那不是那不是
question but that is the answer no let's
问题，但这是答案，不让我们
go further though let's let's let's talk
走得更远，尽管让我们让我们谈论
I would not one right I would that one
我不会一个权利
oh I will give you that yeah
哦，我会给你的
yay modules let's talk about other
yay模块，让我们谈谈其他
features so let's look at the garbage
功能，让我们来看一下垃圾
collection because this is something
收集，因为这是东西
that does mix Java great and from the
确实将Java与
beginning of the times we had the
时代的开始，我们有了
managed memory and we all use
托管内存，我们都使用
application Reese were the hardware
应用程序Reese是硬件
resource and the memory as it is
资源和原样的内存
infinite and it is absolutely perfect so
无限，而且绝对完美，所以
what comes in John 9 it comes the new
约翰福音9章讲的是新的
default garbage collector called g1 GC
默认的垃圾收集器称为g1 GC
if you think of the Java heap Java
如果您想到Java堆Java
memory you probably think of a picture
你可能会想到一张照片的记忆
of something like this you have the heap
这样的东西你有堆
it is separated in different regions
它被分隔在不同的区域
there is the Eden space where the new
有伊甸园空间，新的
objects are allocated and then when they
对象被分配，然后当它们
live long enough if they're survivors
如果幸存者活得足够长
they get promoted to the Turner space
他们被提升到特纳太空
and then they become the old generation
然后他们成为老一辈
the hypothesis here is very simple the
这里的假设很简单
old objects that already survived a
已经幸存下来的旧物件
couple of GC cycles the problem will
几个GC周期问题将
survive more so it doesn't make sense to
生存更多，所以没有意义
collect the memory from the whole space
从整个空间收集记忆
but it's better to split that into
但最好将其分成
different regions and then you can
不同的地区，然后您就可以
perform smaller garbage collections and
执行较小的垃圾收集并
save time on that so the latency of a
节省时间，这样的延迟
single garbage collection cycle will go
单个垃圾回收周期将过去
down and so now with G 1 GC this concept
下降，所以现在有了G 1 GC这个概念
is pushed into not to the extreme but my
被推到不是极端，而是我的
further what do you want you see does it
更进一步，您希望看到什么
splits your heap into very small regions
将堆分成很小的区域
and then they all are allocated and the
然后他们都被分配了，
objects are allocated in them randomly
对象随机分配在其中
and they still have the type so in some
而且它们仍然具有这种类型
of them there will be young objects in
他们当中会有年轻的物体
some of them will be old objects and the
其中一些将是旧物体，
object moved all the time but the main
对象一直移动，但主体
benefit of that is that the garbage
好处是垃圾
collection can decide how many is those
收集可以决定有多少个
small regions it can collect at any
它可以在任何地方收集的小区域
given moment and through that it can
给定的时刻，通过它可以
control what is the word garbage
控制垃圾这个词是什么
collection pause with that he can do
收集暂停，他可以做
magnificent things first the latency of
宏伟的事物首先是潜伏期
the garbage collection goes down second
垃圾收集下降第二
you can adaptively control that so you
您可以自适应地控制
don't have to have like a spreadsheet of
不必像
JVM options to tune your garbage
JVM选项调整垃圾
collection in fact to tune your garbage
收集实际上是为了调整您的垃圾
collection now what you want to do you
现在收集您想做什么
want to just say this is my requirements
只想说这是我的要求
for the garbage collection process and
用于垃圾收集过程，以及
this is my requirement how much space I
这是我的要求我有多少空间
can sacrifice to achieve that Leighton's
可以牺牲来实现莱顿的
the number and this is all garbage
数字，这都是垃圾
collection tuning that is required with
所需的集合调整
g1g see well there were of course more
g1g很好看，当然还有更多
to that but in a normal conversation we
为此，但在正常对话中
can stop at that so do you want to see
可以在那停下来，所以你想看看
is pretty amazing isn't it yeah and this
真的很棒，不是吗
is how it became to us it came to us it
它是如何变成了我们
was introduced in GDP 6 it was tested so
是在GDP 6中引入的，因此经过了测试
it's a very mature technology you could
这是一项非常成熟的技术
have used that before very many
在很多之前就用过
companies try that tested that on
公司尝试对它进行测试
different workloads and it works
不同的工作负载，并且有效
beautifully and now it is getting to all
漂亮，现在它正在普及
of us in jt9 so when you run your
jt9中的我们，所以当您运行
applications on on Java 9 they will
Java 9上的应用程序，他们将
probably run a little bit faster in
可能在
terms of having smaller garbage
拥有较小垃圾的条件
collection pauses it does trade off some
集合暂停它确实折衷了一些
throughput maximal stupid because the
吞吐量最大愚蠢，因为
garbage do one GC will run concurrently
垃圾做一个GC将同时运行
with the application so not the food
与应用程序，而不是食物
resources for your hardware will be
您硬件的资源将是
available to you but for most
提供给您，但大多数情况下
applications especially for applications
应用，尤其是应用
where the latency is important this is a
延迟很重要的地方
very great thing I think the next one's
我认为下一件很伟大的事情
yours
你的
yeah so to summarize that you get the
是的，所以总结一下，您得到了
faster memory management with superior
具有卓越性能的更快的内存管理
application tricks so is G 1 G C a good
应用技巧，因此G 1 GC很好
thing well some performance experts say
一些性能专家说的很好
yes some performance experts say no
是的，一些性能专家说不
ultimately it really depends on your
最终，这实际上取决于您
application you need to test it with
您需要测试的应用程序
your application but the question is is
您的应用程序，但问题是
G 1 G C exciting in Java 9 well let me
G 1 GC在Java 9中令人兴奋
actually go back to a couple of things
其实回到两件事
this was introduced in JDK 6 was before
这是在JDK 6中引入的
my five-year-old son was born tested and
我五岁的儿子出生时经过测试，
supported in JDK 7 that was before my
在我之前的JDK 7中受支持
five-year-old son was born
五岁的儿子出生
officially the default you see in JDK 9
正式是您在JDK 9中看到的默认值
who cares
谁在乎
you could use it anytime you want it
您可以随时使用它
before JDK 9 just with this switch and
在JDK 9之前，只需使用此开关
if you are using a specific a specific
如果您使用的是特定的
GC in your in your JVM arguments is 19
您的JVM参数中的GC为19
can affect you because you're going to
会影响你，因为你要
continue to use that in JDK 9 so is G 1
继续在JDK 9中使用它，G 1也是如此
GC a good thing yeah probably as it
GC是一件好事，可能是因为
gives you choice is it good in Java in
给您选择是Java很好
JDK 9 well it's killed in JDK 9 is good
在JDK 9中被杀死的JDK 9很好
it is in JDK 8 &amp; 7 &amp; 6
它在JDK 8＆7＆6中
it's always been there pretty much so
一直都在那里
that's my argument as to why G 1 GC
这就是我为什么要使用G 1 GC的观点
isn't a big deal in JDK 9 who agrees
在同意的JDK 9中没什么大不了的
with me that as a result it's not a big
跟我说，结果不算大
deal in JDK 9 okay this might be closer
处理JDK 9好的，这可能会更近
and easily it would meet and go
轻松地相遇并走开
different in Eastern Europe
东欧不同
so who believes it is a good who
所以谁相信这是一个好人
believes it is a really good thing in
相信这是一件非常好的事
JDK 9 or even yeah pretty even okay
JDK 9甚至是，甚至还可以
right next one you're on that J shell
就在下一个你在那个J shell上
who's out of J's L pretty much everyone
谁都从J的L中消失
who loves J shell who hates J shell
谁喜欢J Shell谁讨厌J Shell
right okay good I'm glad cuz I'm good
对，好的，我很高兴，因为我很好
cop here for J shell okay let's stop
警察在这里J壳好吧，让我们停止
good things J shell is a gimmick
好东西，J shell是个mm头
reasonable people I know you can leave
合理的人，我知道你可以离开
you guys because I'm good cop here right
你们，因为我是这里的好警察
so J shell J shell is a ripple in a
所以J shell J shell是
ripple stands for really milk program
涟漪代表真正的牛奶计划
close print Luc know we go read eval
关闭打印Luc知道我们去阅读评估
print loop let's just jump into a demo
打印循环，让我们进入演示
shall we
我们可以
okay thank you
好的谢谢
it's not that kind of repeal it's it's a
不是那种废除，而是
raffle so I just type J shell and that
抽奖，所以我只要输入J shell
puts me into a really nice contour is
使我的轮廓非常好
that is that readable from the back
从背面可以读懂
thumbs-up good right so it puts me into
竖起大拇指很好的权利，所以它使我陷入
a consult Here I am in a console I can
在这里，我可以在控制台中
talk to the JDK I can talk to the shell
与JDK对话我可以与Shell对话
if I wanted to talk to the JDK I just
如果我想和JDK交谈，我只是
put something as simple as one plus two
像一加二一样简单
and that gets me three if I wanted to
如果我想的话，那会让我三个
talk to the shell I just put a slash and
和壳说话，我只放了一个斜线，
as soon as I put a slash I'm not talking
我放下斜线就不说话
to the JDK so I have a number of things
到JDK，所以我有很多事情
I can do so one of the other things I'll
我可以做的另一件事是
mention there is when I put one plus two
提到我放一加二的时候
I didn't actually I didn't actually
我不是我不是
assign it to a variable so what it's
将其分配给变量，所以它是什么
actually done is it's assigned it to a
实际完成的是将其分配给
variable for me with the dollar one if I
如果我给我变一美元
wanted to do something similar like int
想做类似int的事情
X equal 18 I was gonna put underscore up
X等于18我要加下划线
and double underscore cuz I can double
和双下划线，因为我可以加倍
underscore equals two plus three oops
下划线等于二加三
two plus three I noticed my reinhold
二加三我注意到我的控制权
just walked in that's why I did that two
刚走进那就是为什么我做了那两个
plus three and you get five so now it's
加三，你得到五，所以现在
double underscore there how cool is that
双下划线那里有多酷
mark that's brilliant that you've left
标志着您留下的辉煌
that in for us
对我们来说
I type slash me and and that gives me
我输入斜杠，那给了我
that gives me the variate the current
给我变量当前
variables that we've that we've got if I
如果我有我们拥有的变量
wanted to do something interesting like
想做一些有趣的事情
system OS you know you can anyone tell
您知道的系统操作系统任何人都可以告诉
me what's missing there let me just put
我在那里缺少的东西让我放
that at the top what's missing there
在顶部，这里缺少什么
semicolon we can we can code Java
分号，我们可以，我们可以编码Java
without semicolons how good's that it's
没有分号，那有多好
amazing that's work that's worth a whoop
令人惊讶的是值得付出的工作
if nothing else is worth the wait
如果没有别的值得等待
getting just a movie yeah let's dress
只是看电影，我们穿
the red dot
红点
sleep oops Wow no try/catch how cool is
哎呀，哇，不要尝试/赶上它有多酷
that
那
if I if I do I'd know a public void say
如果我愿意的话，我会知道有一个公众空话
hello and then here I can just do
你好，然后在这里我可以做
something like system oops system dot
像系统oops系统点
out dot print me print then hello at
点打印我打印然后打招呼
this point because I'm doing multi lines
这一点是因为我正在做多行
it obviously needs a obviously needs a
它显然需要一个明显需要的
semicolon so when I do that we now have
分号，所以当我这样做时，我们现在有了
a method so i can type slash m and we
一种可以输入斜线m的方法
get a method i can slash edit that say
得到一种方法，我可以斜线编辑说
or two idly did capital say hello and we
一两个闲散的资本会打招呼吗，我们
get this amazing 1970s window pop-up and
得到这个惊人的1970年代的窗口弹出，
from from here i can say hello world i
从这里我可以说你好世界我
can i can say except that and you'll
除了那我能说吗，你会
notice that that that has actually
请注意，实际上
updated there i can exit i can execute
更新在那里我可以退出我可以执行
that apologies for for making that a
对此致歉，
capital s by the way and we get hollow
顺便说一句，我们变得空洞
well so i can do that we can also add
好吧，我可以做到，我们也可以添加
classes and things like that if i wanted
类和类似的东西，如果我想
so i excite coops so I can say class a
所以我很兴奋，所以我可以说A级
we get a class a I can say interface
我们得到一个我可以说接口的类
interface B we get our interface I can
接口B我们可以得到我们的接口
type slash team we get our type so it's
斜线团队我们得到了我们的类型
it's pretty much just you know using
几乎就是您知道使用的
using a used a rebel before for up with
使用之前使用过的叛军
other languages just yeah it's great we
其他语言，是的，我们很棒
can we can use there is I think it's
我们可以使用那里吗，我认为是
Java repel comm was what we could use
Java排斥通讯是我们可以使用的
previously but this is nicely connected
以前但是这很好地连接
straight into the open JDK yeah other
直接进入开放的JDK是的，其他
things like you can check what's
像你可以检查的东西
imported other things if I wanted to I
如果我想导入其他东西
can just type list and I can see
可以只输入列表，我可以看到
everything that I've typed in to the JDK
我在JDK中输入的所有内容
I can also type to slash history and I
我也可以输入以削减历史记录
get everything that I've typed whether
得到我键入的所有内容是否
to the JDK or to the console itself if I
到JDK或控制台本身（如果我
wanted to I can save that as commands I
想我可以将其保存为命令
can slash research which resets my state
可以大刀阔斧地进行研究，从而重拾我的状态
so if I now type slash P I get nothing
因此，如果我现在输入斜杠PI，则一无所获
but what I can do is I can open commands
但我能做的是打开命令
and this is actually just saving it as a
这实际上只是将其保存为
as a text file and now it's run
作为文本文件，现在可以运行
everything so you saw that one second
一切，所以你看到那一秒钟
repair delay then you saw the you know
维修延迟，然后您就知道了
the creation of everything then you see
一切的创造，然后你看到
hello world so that's J so taste it was
你好，世界，所以J
pretty pretty awesome one other thing
相当不错的另一件事
actually if I slash exit this is our
其实如果我斜线退出，这是我们的
only user venkat line here depending on
这里只有用户venkat行，具体取决于
how how
怎么样
you're feeling at the time you can exit
您当时感觉可以退出
in two different ways you can either
您可以通过两种不同的方式
command D if you're feeling you know
如果您感到知道，则命令D
like you don't really want anyone to
就像你真的不想要任何人
talk to you if you're feeling a bit down
与您交谈，如果您感到有点沮丧
if you're feeling down and you need some
如果您情绪低落，需要一些
you need a hug
你需要一个拥抱
just type slash accent it says goodbye
只需输入斜杠重音即可说再见
so there we go right if you if you type
因此，如果您输入以下内容，我们就可以了
J shell and you just type printing
J shell，您只需键入打印
something something very very nice that
一些非常非常好的东西
we get a little bit mucky and that all
我们变得有点烂了
it all it actually does is if if look at
它实际上所做的就是如果看
the methods it provides me the whole
它为我提供整体的方法
list of prints so I can then type I can
打印清单，这样我就可以输入
type print hello or hell up whichever
输入print hello或hell up up
you choose and and you know it's much
您选择，而且您知道很多
much nice you don't have to
很好，您不必
system.out.print Leland's different
system.out.print Leland的与众不同
things like that one thing I will say
我会说一件事
which is absolutely awesome and it's
绝对很棒，
great that mark syndrome actually cuz
那个马克综合症实际上很棒
I'll say it I'll say it so marking here
我会说，所以我会在这里标记
I'm sure he said it before Haydn's
我敢肯定他在海顿之前就说了
converts did a really really great
转换者做得非常好
videos about 30 minutes long or so and
大约30分钟左右的视频
one thing he did was he actually created
他做的一件事是他实际上创造了
a a script with a with a hash Bank and
一个带有哈希银行的脚本，并且
passing in J shell and then a scripted
传入J Shell，然后编写脚本
system with some Java code and by doing
一些Java代码并通过
that you can actually execute J shell as
您实际上可以执行J Shell
if you were like a bash script or
如果您像一个bash脚本或
something like that if it throws an
如果它抛出一个类似的东西
exception I don't know if it still does
例外，我不知道它是否仍然
that maybe throws an exception but you
也许会引发异常，但是你
can ignore that and then just runs runs
可以忽略它，然后运行
Java like a script how cool is that
Java就像脚本一样，那有多酷
but yeah there's J shell brilliant
但是，是的，J Shell很棒
brilliant brilliant and over to you for
辉煌的辉煌，为您服务
a bad cop yeah we yep jeschill is
是个坏警察，是的，耶瑟尔是
brilliant and it's gonna change it we
辉煌，它将改变我们
help people learn Java and help people
帮助人们学习Java和帮助人们
get into using Java especially the small
开始使用Java尤其是小型Java
humans children children and agile is
人类的孩子儿童和敏捷是
pretty amazing at the same time it's
同时非常令人惊讶
really hard to imagine that Jo would
很难想象乔会
change the way we develop software it's
改变我们开发软件的方式
pretty hard to type in like a
很难像
significantly large program into a
很大的程序变成了
single show there is this reason why
单秀有这个原因
Simon didn't show you how to create an
西蒙（Simon）没有向您展示如何创建
annotation
注解
there is no reason you can presentations
没有理由可以发表演讲
in jail but it just takes a little bit
在监狱里，但只需要一点点
more typing so while it's a it's a great
更多的打字，所以这是一个伟大的
thing it feels a little bit gimmicky
感觉有点花哨
personally I would love to see the
我个人很想看看
future where you can connect your Jay
未来可以连接杰伊的地方
shell to running JVM process Java
外壳程序以运行JVM进程Java
process write and execute commands
处理写和执行命令
within the context of that process I as
在那个过程中我
far as I know currently you cannot do
据我目前所知，你做不到
that you can embed gesso and create like
您可以嵌入gesso并创建像
a console in your app but you have to
应用中的控制台，但您必须
think about that when beforehand and if
事先考虑一下，如果
you think about that beforehand it
你事先考虑一下
doesn't count so yeah I it's a gesture
不算数，是的，我这是一个手势
it's a gimmick all are the languages
这是一个mm头，所有的语言
have that now Java has that as well
现在有了Java
yeah Java so who believes Jay shell is
是的Java谁相信Jay Shell是
an interesting tool and you'll probably
一个有趣的工具，您可能会
use it to test our API it's and things
用它来测试我们的API
without having to know support up a
无需知道支持
whole browser and browser ID and do a
整个浏览器和浏览器ID并执行
whole bunch of extra things who likes
一大堆喜欢的东西
the idea of just coding quick okay okay
只是编码的想法很快就好了
who here uses a proper IDE and hasn't
谁在这里使用适当的IDE而没有
done Java development in VI or Emacs for
在VI或Emacs中完成Java开发
ages and the Omar IDs supports some sort
年龄和Omar ID支持某种形式
of like evaluation of expressions words
评价表达词的方式
like scratch pads or something and they
像便笺本之类的东西，他们
know that they will almost never touch
知道他们几乎永远不会碰
the Jay shell at real job except for
杰伊·壳（Jay shell）在实际工作中
testing racket or something
测试球拍之类的
all right so modules modules are thumbs
好吧，所以模块模块是大拇指
up do you want you see it was in draw
你想不想看到它在抽奖中
and I think draw for JC already right
而且我认为为JC开奖已经正确了
it's 50/50 for me API updates we can't
对我来说是50/50，我们无法更新API
really be a bad cop on API updates so
真的对API更新不满意，所以
we're gonna both be good cop for API
我们都会成为API的好警察
updates because the API updates are
更新，因为API更新是
always pretty awesome for Java
Java总是很棒
developers so so you're gonna do the
开发人员，这样您就可以
demo right yeah and yours well here
演示对，是的，您也可以在这里
other than yours come on I mean
除了你的，我的意思是
obviously I'm gonna show you the new API
显然，我要向您展示新的API
using the gimmicky J show whoa
使用花哨的J表演哇
I don't want to change their vote now
我现在不想更改他们的投票
[Applause]
[掌声]
this is not my machine so my typing will
这不是我的机器，所以我的打字会
be a little bit slow but we'll manage if
有点慢，但我们会设法
we run out of time please just tell me
我们时间用完了，请告诉我
that we need to cover other things
我们需要涵盖其他事情
because there are many many API
因为有很多API
improvements in channel 9 right and we
第9频道的改善，我们
will not go through all of them I'll
不会经历所有的人，我会
show you a couple of that I like the
给你看几个我喜欢的
most or I think they're the most
最多，或者我认为他们是最多的
affluent influential maybe and we'll see
富有的影响力也许，我们会看到
how much we can I do so one thing that
我能做到的一件事
we wanted from Java for ages right and
我们想要Java的年龄合适，
everyone thought that this would be
每个人都认为这将是
absolutely great to have that work
从事这项工作绝对很棒
collection literals so we don't need to
集合文字，因此我们不需要
create the new early list and then the
创建新的早期列表，然后
subsequent statements populate that with
随后的语句填充
data now we have those the collection
数据，现在我们有了那些集合
leaders in Java are here just getting
Java的领导者来了
the note collection leaders there are
那里的便笺收集负责人
factoring methods because we're talking
因数方法，因为我们正在谈论
about Java so but the thing what we can
关于Java，但是我们可以做的事情
do you can talk about you can create a
你可以谈谈你可以创建一个
list of elements or a set of elements in
中的元素列表或一组元素
a single line of code and you populate
一行代码，然后填充
that and it is a fully functional
那是一个功能齐全的
implementation of the list interface
列表接口的实现
over you can do a set and you just type
结束，你可以做一个集合，你只要输入
off and you do the elements and you have
离开，你做的元素，你有
a set you can also do a map where you
一套你也可以做一张地图
will just provide the key and entry
将只提供密钥和条目
values in in a row and it will create a
值连续，它将创建一个
map back to you the good thing about
映射回你的好东西
this is that while it simplifies the
这是因为它简化了
syntax it also does very important
语法也很重要
things the implementations of those
那些东西的实现
classes are very interesting so if I do
课程非常有趣，所以如果我这样做
this and do get class what I think will
这并获得我认为会的课程
get who thinks that will get an array
得到谁认为会得到数组的人
list a few people who think I'll get a
列出一些认为我会得到
linked list smart so in fact I will get
链表很聪明，所以实际上我会得到
new implementation that was just added
刚刚添加的新实现
in the Java 9 and it's an immutable list
在Java 9中，这是一个不可变的列表
of one element and one of the things is
一要素之一是
those implementations are fairly heavily
这些实现相当繁重
optimized so that for example it stores
经过优化，例如可以存储
the element in the field so with passive
领域中的元素，所以与被动
doesn't need to do that in the array
不需要在数组中这样做
access so it just reads element directly
访问，因此它只是直接读取元素
because it's mutable in contains one
因为它的可变性包含一个
element and so on if you have lists of
元素，依此类推，如果您有
two elements it's also heavily optimized
两个要素也进行了优化
and there are like a collection of n
而且有一个n的集合
elements and further
要素及进一步
so those collection literals will make
因此这些收集文字将使
your code more readable and it's going
您的代码更具可读性
to be absolutely great to use those one
绝对好用那些
other interesting thing actually when
其他有趣的事情
you've got that gate class if you just
如果你只是有门课程
grab that again off that gate class you
再从那门课上抓住你
can actually do a dot i think as it is
我实际上可以做一个点
it get module module just have it yeah
它得到模块模块就可以了
get module so if you don't get module
获取模块，所以如果您不获取模块
there you'll actually see you can
在那里，您实际上会看到可以
actually see which module that came from
实际看到来自哪个模块
which is kind of nice interesting thing
这是一件很有趣的事情
to know about one here yep and then you
在这里知道一个人然后你
remembered if you're still in class pass
记得你还在上课
and everything is great so besides that
一切都很棒，除此之外
there are a couple of things that so in
有几件事是这样的
John eight we got the stream API and got
约翰八世，我们得到了流API，
optional sanjana and those are really
可选的sanjana，那些真的
great and then in John 9 there are a
太好了，然后在约翰福音9章中有一个
couple of improvements one of my
几个改进之一
favorite is the stream method on the
最喜欢的是流方法
optional so what you can do now is
可选，所以您现在可以做的是
optional of say 1 and I can do a stream
说1的可选内容，我可以进行直播
of it and I get the stream
它，我得到了流
implementation while it seems like a
实施，虽然看起来像
unreasonable thing to do because an
做不合理的事情，因为
optional provides you with the swim like
可选为您提供游泳
methods for mapping functions or the
映射函数的方法或
values within the optional container
可选容器中的值
it's very important so if I do this
这很重要，所以如果我这样做
27:27 and I do a map function here so I
27:27我在这里做地图功能，所以我
haven't an apply function whatever get
没有任何应用功能
say x times 2 what will I get back
说x乘2我会得到什么
will I get 4 will I get an optional 4 or
我会得到4我会得到可选的4还是
1 to my mass is terrible
1对我的群众来说太可怕了
no in fact I will since stream is lazy
其实我不会，因为流很懒
by default now if a convert optional
现在默认情况下，如果转换可选
into a stream I will get the laziness of
变成溪流，我会变得懒惰
the stream in my optional so back I will
在我的可选流，所以回来我会
get the reference pipeline and we'll
获取参考管道，我们将
need a terminal operation to actually
需要终端操作才能真正
in evaluate the function that they
在评估他们的功能
provided if I do just a normal thing
如果我只是做正常的事情而提供
optional of one and I will do a map
一个可选，我会做一张地图
immediately here I will get the result
立即在这里，我会得到结果
immediately so if you have a functions
立即开始，如果您有功能
you might your mapping the functions
您可能会映射功能
which are expensive performance wise and
在性能上是昂贵的
you don't mainly really need to evaluate
您基本上不需要真的进行评估
them early you can always convert an
他们很早就可以转换
optional tea stream very very easily
可选茶流非常非常容易
another cool thing that is present in
存在的另一个很酷的东西
the optional optional
可选的
what is it empty let's do the empty one
什么是空的，让我们做空的
previously we had the method called if
以前我们有一个叫做if的方法
present which would take a function
存在的功能
which will evaluate only the if the
仅当
value in the optional is present now we
现在可选值​​存在
can have the method that takes two
可以有两种方法
arguments and it called it is called if
参数，它被称为如果
present or else and it takes two
现在，否则需要两个
functions so if it is present then we
功能，所以如果它存在，那么我们
have a function and we do I think we
有功能，我认为我们
need this side effect here do you start
在这里需要这种副作用吗？
with drinking yes print X and if it's
与喝是打印X，如果它是
not then we just have a supplier and we
不那么我们只有供应商，我们
do print empty I hope this works
确实打印为空，我希望这行得通
empty you can never know if it works not
空的你永远不知道它是否行不通
you know why because we're in J show I
你知道为什么，因为我们在J秀中
love to I love the way I love the way it
爱我爱我爱的方式
took about four times to do that because
大概花了四次
you actually the smiley instead of a
你实际上是笑脸而不是
quiet thing I'm fairly optimistic person
安静的东西我是相当乐观的人
very rarely I'm a bad cop so there are a
我很少是一个坏警察，所以有一个
couple of things on the stream API so if
流API上的几件事，如果
I take in stream and if I will type that
我参加了直播，如果要输入
correctly and then we'll do a range from
正确，然后我们将
1 to 10 now we have the methods to drop
现在有1到10
elements while and take while which are
while元素和take while元素
pretty interesting they also present in
他们也参加了
all other stream implementations and now
所有其他流实现以及现在
we'll have them built in the JDK as well
我们也将它们内置在JDK中
so say we can drop the elements until a
所以说我们可以删除元素直到
certain condition is met and X more than
满足特定条件且X大于
5 and then after that we will for each
5之后，我们将为每个
will print
将打印
this element when we see we drop the
当我们看到这个元素时，
first five elements also you can just
前五个元素也可以
take a number of elements in it from
从中吸收许多元素
your stream it's very useful if you just
您的信息流，如果您只是
need like say like five elements but not
需要说像五个要素，但不是
the five elements but like you need to
这五个要素，但就像你需要
take the events until some condition is
进行事件，直到出现某种情况
met for example you want to skip the
例如遇到您要跳过
duplicate events or something so the
重复事件或其他
stream API was enhanced as well one
流API也得到了增强
thing one thing I like about this
我喜欢这件事
actually is the take wall so for example
其实就是拿墙，例如
if you actually had an infinite stream
如果您实际上有无限的流
and you don't want it to continue
而你不希望它继续下去
running and running and running you
运行并运行您
might say I'm gonna take while while
可能会说我要花一会儿
some other condition is met and then
满足一些其他条件，然后
when something once I'm billion hits
当我有十亿的命中
true then you stop that infinite stream
是的，那么你就停止那无限的流
you know I'm going to kill a process to
你知道我要杀死一个进程
kill that streams as can be quite
杀死那条溪流
interesting as well yep and another
是的，还有有趣的
thing that was added was the iterate
添加的是迭代
method where you can do the proper
您可以做适当的方法
iteration and we'll need to check the
迭代，我们需要检查
syntax on that so you start with the
语法，所以您从
start value then you do the increment
起始值，然后进行增量
step and then you specify a condition
步骤，然后您指定一个条件
and before John I it was quite clumsy to
在约翰一世之前，
do that because there was no iterate
这样做是因为没有迭代
method to do that but now we can do that
做到这一点的方法，但现在我们可以做到这一点
if it's less than 10 and then we for
如果小于10，那么我们
each would print them and
每个人都会打印它们，
is the other way around see a proper ID
另一种方法是查看正确的ID
would suggest me to do that I should
会建议我这样做，我应该
know this is exactly like a for loop but
知道这就像一个for循环，但是
now you can generate streams normally
现在您可以正常生成流
like you do because you have some
喜欢你，因为你有一些
condition and then from sequence of
条件，然后从
values a I have the step and it's a
值一个我有步骤，这是一个
fairly interesting API to play with
相当有趣的API
there were some improvements for local
当地有一些改进
data time there are some improvements
数据时间有一些改善
for the process handles the process a
对于流程处理流程
process management is interesting
流程管理很有趣
because before it was so messy in Java 9
因为以前在Java 9中是如此混乱
and then we'll just show you that thing
然后我们将向您展示那件事
and then we'll go to the next of next
然后我们转到下一个下一个
things there are also concurrency
东西也有并发
improvements the completely future got a
改进，完全是未来
couple of new methods there were also
还有一些新方法
reactive classes in the like flow so we
像流这样的反应性类，所以我们
can get closer to the reactive
可以更接近反应性
programming mainly in jdk 18 3 or
主要在jdk 18 3中编程或
whatever the version ends up being but
无论版本最终是
with the process process handle there is
与过程的过程句柄有
a new class and you can do the process
新课，你可以做这个过程
handle current you can do the sub
处理当前你可以做的子
process management fairly easily so you
流程管理相当容易，所以您
can get the current process you can then
可以获得当前流程，然后
execute some info and get some arguments
执行一些信息并获取一些参数
and yet you can get the arguments for
但是你可以得到
any processes you can get the process
任何可以获取流程的流程
representation in your Java code so if
Java代码中的表示形式，因此，如果
you deal with sub processes or if you
您处理子流程，或者
need to check any arguments you can
需要检查您可以的任何参数
differentiate with mudan processes much
与木丹工艺区别很大
easier this is also cross-platform which
更容易，这也是跨平台的
is fairly great because now around
相当不错，因为现在
everything runs in docker so now we
一切都在docker中运行，所以现在我们
especially need that cross-platform
特别需要跨平台
things there are a bunch of improvements
事情有很多改进
my personal favorite is that now we can
我个人最喜欢的是，现在我们可以
read the property files in utf-8 there
在其中读取utf-8中的属性文件
is exactly one method that supports that
正是一种支持这一点的方法
but we can do that so if you can find it
但我们可以这样做，所以如果您能找到它
that's very cool
太酷了
the single underscore is not supported
不支持下划线
this is now unreasonable to type a thing
现在输入东西是不合理的
like this what
像这样
will happen if he sleep enter an
如果他入睡会发生
exception right there is no type I don't
例外权，没有我没有的类型
know that there is no keyboard keyword
知道没有键盘关键字
if I do just to two underscores just
如果我只对两个下划线做
like Simon did I will have the name that
像西蒙一样，我的名字是
there is no variable type inference
没有变量类型推断
sufficient enough and we will do but you
足够，我们会做，但是你
can use two keywords so you're going to
可以使用两个关键字，所以您将
check your source code for single
检查您的源代码是否为单个
underscores and then you can wear that
下划线，然后你可以穿
other in API language improvements you
其他API语言方面的改进
can have private methods in the
可以在
interfaces so now with the default
现在使用默认界面
methods in private methods you can
您可以使用私有方法中的方法
actually put a lot of logic in your
实际上在你的逻辑上
interfaces which is amazingly great and
界面很棒，而且
there are a couple other things
还有其他几件事
oh let me just check yeah if you use try
哦，让我检查一下是否可以使用
with resources this is fantastic this is
有资源，这太棒了，这是
not the API improvement language you
不是您使用的API改进语言
prune they try with resources blocks now
修剪他们现在尝试使用资源块
you can use effectively final variables
您可以有效地使用最终变量
in the try with resources so you don't
尝试使用资源，这样您就不会
need to declare them within this little
需要在这一点内声明它们
line of the try block but you can
try块的行，但是您可以
declare them of somewhere above and then
将它们声明在上方某处，然后
use them reference them in the try with
使用它们在尝试中引用它们
resources block and they will be closed
资源块，它们将被关闭
automatically at the end of that try
在尝试结束时自动
block so that makes the code much more
块，使代码更多
readable but it's really hard to show in
可读性强，但很难显示
JSON so but we're still super excited
JSON，但我们仍然非常兴奋
for the for therefore the API
对于for API
improvements okay so here okay so the
改进好吧，所以在这里好吧，
final few things that will we'll talk
最后几件事，我们将谈论
about HTTP to HTTPS project rather than
关于HTTP到HTTPS项目而不是
being in the full full JDK which is what
在完整的完整JDK中，这是什么
I mentioned before so I where talk about
我之前提到过，所以我在哪里谈论
up for too long this is your slide I
太久了，这是你的幻灯片
like I don't know why you picked this
就像我不知道你为什么选择这个
this page it's a picture of a full
此页面是完整图片
Google search angry hipster and this was
谷歌搜索生气的时髦，这是
because the jason-- jason-- libraries
因为jason-- jason--库
and jason manipulation did not make it
和杰森操纵没有做到这一点
into jdk 9 which is very great because
进入jdk 9，这非常好，因为
we have plenty of third-party
我们有很多第三方
implementations and you can choose
实现，您可以选择
whatever my currently personally is
无论我目前的个人身份是什么
marshy I think by Square but yeah some
沼泽，我认为是Square，但是，是的
hipsters might be angry about that you
赶时髦的人可能会对你生气
save the best till last
保存最好直到最后
html5 Java Docs and it is searchable
html5 Java文档，它是可搜索的
yeah say you couldn't type in that the
是的，您无法输入
hang on see this little search box right
等一下，看看这个小搜寻框
on the side here you can type something
在这边你可以输入一些东西
in today I think you can actually just
在今天，我想你实际上可以
say for completable future for example I
比如说我的未来
think you can just do capital C capital
认为你可以做资本C资本
F it's all right muck capital C capital
F没关系，可以算是资本C资本
F in it all it'll actually do the search
F实际上，它实际上会进行搜索
for completable futures well I'm pretty
对于完好的期货，我很漂亮
sure it does that so yeah you can you
确保这样做，是的，你可以
can pretty much search for whatever you
几乎可以搜索任何东西
want known as a smart search so yeah
想要被称为智能搜索，是的
welcome to 2005 with that one
欢迎来到2005年
anyway with a few minutes left maybe a
无论如何，还剩下几分钟
couple of minutes left
还剩几分钟
two minutes left so any questions maybe
还有两分钟，所以可能有任何问题
before Leo questions because a couple of
在狮子座提问之前，因为
people are starting to leave let's do
人们开始离开让我们做
another one so before there were a
另一个，所以在有一个之前
couple of people who are not excited
几个不兴奋的人
about gamma 9 let's try that again
关于伽玛9，让我们再试一次
who is excited about Java 9 release who
谁对Java 9发布感到兴奋
thinks that it's a fairly medium curve
认为这是一条中等曲线
release as they go there were a few
他们走的时候有一些
before but J shall I think so I'll say
以前，但我会认为J，所以我会说
I'll say a big thank you for everyone
我会非常感谢大家
for turning up we love presenting at
对于出现，我们喜欢在
JavaOne so thank you for the full room
JavaOne，谢谢您的整个房间
please please please if you could vote
请可以请你投票
for our session that would be awesome
对于我们的会议来说太棒了
I will not you know actually as I was
我不会像我以前那样知道
walking in the guys told me that the
走在伙计们告诉我，
yellow and the red buttons don't
黄色和红色按钮不
actually work so yeah if you feel like
实际工作，是的，如果你觉得
pressing the green button would
按下绿色按钮会
appreciate that very much thank you very
非常感谢你
much
许多
and if you don't like the presentation
如果您不喜欢演示文稿
you can use J rebel to redeem your sixty
您可以使用J rebel赎回您的六十岁
minutes back thank you
分钟前谢谢